{
    "subject": "resource/Anne_Sjerp_Troelstra",
    "predicate": "ontology/doctoralStudent",
    "object": "resource/Laurina_Verbrugge",
    "human_readable": "Anne Sjerp Troelstra was a doctoral student of Laurina Verbrugge.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885850548744202,
            "question": "Did Laurina Verbrugge supervise a doctoral student named Anne Sjerp Troelstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9698053598403931,
            "question": "Was Anne Sjerp Troelstra a student?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9271713495254517,
            "question": "Was Anne Sjerp Troelstra a PhD candidate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9263312816619873,
            "question": "What was Laurina Verbrugge's role in relation to Anne Sjerp Troelstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9237693548202515,
            "question": "Who was Anne Sjerp Troelstra's doctoral advisor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9190524220466614,
            "question": "Who guided Anne Sjerp Troelstra through her doctoral studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8931933045387268,
            "question": "In what capacity did Laurina Verbrugge work with Anne Sjerp Troelstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8629164695739746,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Anne Sjerp Troelstra and Laurina Verbrugge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8283371329307556,
            "question": "What is the nature of the connection between Anne Sjerp Troelstra and Laurina Verbrugge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8080561757087708,
            "question": "To whom did Anne Sjerp Troelstra submit her doctoral thesis?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Anne Sjerp Troelstra was a doctoral student of Laurina Verbrugge.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7588_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nature of the connection between Anne Sjerp Troelstra and Laurina Verbrugge?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7588_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Anne Sjerp Troelstra and Laurina Verbrugge?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7588_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what capacity did Laurina Verbrugge work with Anne Sjerp Troelstra?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7588_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7588_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7588_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7588_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7588_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7588_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7588_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7588_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7588_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7588_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7588_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not mention Laurina Verbrugge as an advisor or supervisor of Anne Sjerp Troelstra, nor does it provide any information about him being a doctoral student of hers. According to the documents, Arend Heyting was his advisor."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The provided documents do not mention Anne Sjerp Troelstra being a doctoral student of Laurina Verbrugge. Instead, the documents indicate that he was advised by Arend Heyting for his doctorate and mentions some students who were close to him (Olga Bakker and Dick de Jongh), but does not specify their advisor or their relationship with Troelstra as advisors."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information in the context suggesting that Anne Sjerp Troelstra was a doctoral student of Laurina Verbrugge.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The text states that Anne Sjerp Troelstra's interests converged on intuitionism with Arend Heyting as his advisor.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Laurina Verbrugge as Anne Sjerp Troelstra's doctoral advisor or supervisor in the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions Arend Heyting as Anne Sjerp Troelstra's advisor, not Laurina Verbrugge.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}